http://shatzusa.com/privacy-policy/

Quote is Empty
Like us on Facebook!
Contact Us
Call Us!
800-292-0292
We are Available Monday-Friday
8:30 - 5:00 EST
Search for:
Search
Business to Business
sales@shatzusa.com NEW! Check out our online Catalogs!
MenuNew and Popular ProductsWoven & Printed LabelsCustom & HD Woven LabelsDie & Laser CutSatin Woven LabelsSize LabelsWoven Damask LabelsWoven Taffeta Labels ClosePrinted LabelsBar Coded & QR Coded LabelsHang TagsHeat Transfers & FusiblesMatte PolyesterTyvekReemaySatinTaffetaTwill CloseMade in USA Labels, Tags & Patches CloseSnaps, Fasteners & ButtonsSpecialty Fasteners & ButtonsSnap Sets & Jean Tack ButtonsSnap & Tack FinishesSnap TapeKick Press Machine & Die Sets CloseZippers & Zipper PullsMetal ZippersMolded ZippersNylon Coil ZippersZipper Pulls CloseCords, Cord Locks & TipsCordsCord LocksCord Ends & TipsCustom Cord locks CloseElastic, Patches & TrimsWoven & Embroidered PatchesWoven ElasticWoven BraidsLogo Webbing & Lanyard’sBias Tape / BindingFancy TrimsAppliques CloseBuckles, Closures & ClipsBra Closures & SlidesBucklesFashion & Costume Belt Slides & BucklesHook & Eye ClosuresSlides & Dee Rings Close
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
WE DO NOT SHARE DATA IN ANY WAY SHAPE OR FORM
Who we are
Our website address is: http://www.shatzusa.com.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Contact forms
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
Analytics
Who we share your data with & How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Your contact information
Product Categories
Kick Press Machine & Die Sets
Shock, Cotton & Poly Cords
Elastic
Satin Elastic Bra Straps
Satin Elastic Bra Straps
Woven & Printed Labels
800-292-0292
Like us on Facebook!
About Us
My Account
Policy Information
Privacy Policy
FAQ – Frequently Asked Questions
Contact Us
© 2020 Norman Shatz Co USA All Rights Reserved
English
Arabic Chinese (Simplified) Chinese (Traditional) Czech English French German Indonesian Italian Japanese Korean Portuguese Russian Sindhi Spanish Thai
Menu
New and Popular ProductsWoven & Printed Labels
Custom & HD Woven Labels
Die & Laser CutSatin Woven LabelsSize LabelsWoven Damask LabelsWoven Taffeta Labels Back
Printed Labels
Bar Coded & QR Coded LabelsHang TagsHeat Transfers & FusiblesMatte PolyesterTyvekReemaySatinTaffetaTwill Back
Made in USA Labels, Tags & Patches Back
Snaps, Fasteners & Buttons
Specialty Fasteners & ButtonsSnap Sets & Jean Tack ButtonsSnap & Tack FinishesSnap TapeKick Press Machine & Die Sets Back
Zippers & Zipper Pulls
Metal ZippersMolded ZippersNylon Coil ZippersZipper Pulls Back
Cords, Cord Locks & Tips
CordsCord LocksCord Ends & TipsCustom Cord locks Back
Elastic, Patches & Trims
Woven & Embroidered PatchesWoven ElasticWoven BraidsLogo Webbing & Lanyard’sBias Tape / BindingFancy TrimsAppliques Back
Buckles, Closures & Clips
Bra Closures & SlidesBucklesFashion & Costume Belt Slides & BucklesHook & Eye ClosuresSlides & Dee Rings Back
Like us on Facebook!About UsMy AccountPolicy InformationPrivacy PolicyFAQ – Frequently Asked QuestionsContact Us
